<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tour&amp;Travel</string>
    <string name="sajek_text">

        Sajak Valley is located on the border of Mizoram in the southernmost district
        of Rangamati district. Sajak is the largest union of Bangladesh, whose area is
        702 square miles. Tripura to the north of Sajek, Longadu of Rangamati on the
        south, Mizoram of India on the east, Dighinala of Khagrachari on the west. Although
        Sajak is located in Rangamati district, its travel facility is from Dighinalala of
        Khagrachari. Coming from Rangamati via Kaptai by way of water, there are many ways to
        go sajake. It is 70 kms away from Khagrachari district headquarters. And 49 kilometers
        from Dighinala 34 kilometers from Baghaihat.

    </string>
    <string name="sundarban_text">

       The Sundarbans mangrove forest, one of the largest such forests in the world (140,000 ha), lies on the delta of the Ganges, Brahmaputra and Meghna rivers on the Bay of Bengal.
       It is adjacent to the border of India’s Sundarbans World Heritage site inscribed in 1987.
       The site is intersected by a complex network of tidal waterways, mudflats and small islands of salt-tolerant mangrove forests, and presents an excellent example of ongoing ecological processes.
       The area is known for its wide range of fauna, including 260 bird species, the Bengal tiger and other threatened species such as the estuarine crocodile and the Indian python.

    </string>

    <string name="thanchi_text">

        Tindu is a village of Thanchi Upazila under Bandarban District. It is known as an attractive tourist destination for adventure-loving tourists. Sky, fog, cloud, river, stones, hills, waterfall, forest, blue green water and mystery thrillers fear – if you want to get all of these at a time, then you should go to Tindu. Two corridors have gone on the two sides of Tindu and all day long from those, water comes out with crystal clean flows. The biggest feature is, in the rainy season clouds can be touched on the boat. A white-black museum of water and stone is formed around this village. It is an area of clouds, area of fogs, a land of rocky water.

    </string>

    <string name="patenga_text">
        Patenga Beach is one of the renowned beaches in Bangladesh. For watching sunset, Patenga is a beautiful sea beach close to Chittagong city. It is near the beginning of the Karnaphuli River. Nature lovers come here to enjoy the beautiful scenario of the Bay of Bengal and get away from busy city life. Patenga is a popular tourist spot. The beach is very close to Bangladesh Naval Academy of Bangladesh Navy, and Shah Amanat International Airport. The width of the beach is narrow and swimming is not recommended in the seas here.
        As part of the sea shore a concrete walls can be seen along the shore. Also large blocks of stones have been laid out to prevent erosion. During 1990s lots of restaurants and kiosks have been developed around the beach area. Lighting of the beach area has enhanced the security aspect of night visit. People visiting this beautiful place usually wake up early to witness the stunning sunrise.

    </string>

    <string name="saint_martin_text">


     St. Martin (Island) is the only coral island in Bangladesh a small island St. Martin is in the northeast part of the Bay of Bengal, about 9 km south of the tip of the Coxs Bazar-Teknaf peninsula.
      It is about 8 km west of the northwest coast of Myanmar at the mouth of the Naf River. Also called (The local name) "Narical Gingira", also spelled "Narikel Janjina/Jinjera" and has an extension named Chera Dwip.
    </string>


    <string name="jaflong_text">

        In the Gowainghat Upazila of Sylhet district in Bangladesh, very popular tourist
        attraction Jaflong is visited by thousands of not only local but tourists from all
        over the world every year. Located northeast region of Bangladesh, 12596 sqm. Area
        of Sylhet division has a population of 7.899 million. This city has a distinctly
        different culture of its own. Their colloquial language including their Bengali
        language mixed with other for example, Arabic, Farsi, Hindi, Urdu languages.
        As you drive here, you can see the fascinating waterfalls and hills of various
        sizes from afar. Specifically, wonderful location is at the border between
        Bangladesh and India known as the Zero point. Tamabil is the border area only
        5 km from there. If you want to go to India, there is the immigration checkpoint
        where you need to show a valid visa. Beyond the border lies the state of Meghalaya,
        India. Shillong is the capital of the state. The same rule applies for India
        citizens who wish to visit Bangladesh.

    </string>

    <string name="coxsbazar_text">

         Coxs Bazar is one of the most visited tourist destinations in Bangladesh,
        although not a major international tourist destination. In 2013, the Bangladesh
        Government formed the Tourist Police unit to protect local and foreign tourists
        better, as well as to look after the nature and wildlife in the tourist spots
        of Coxs Bazar.The beach is the main attraction of the town. There are several
        3 stars and 5 star hotels provide the exclusive beachside area with accessories
        for the tourist. Visitors in other hotels visit the Laboni beach which is the
        area of the beach closest to the town. Other than the beach there are several
        places of interest near the town which can easily be visited from the town center.

    </string>

    <string name="bangladesh">
        Bangladesh is a land of mystery and intrigue. The country is centuries old and while 
        it has seen many visitors over the years, it is only now starting to experience a 
        commercial tourism boom. In many respects, Bangladesh is a land of opportunity and 
        adventure.
        All you need do is step out and discover its many mysteries for yourself.
        Come and explore Bangladesh with us..
    </string>

    <string name="kuakata_text">
        Kuakata is known for its picturesque landscape beauty of panoramic beach, clear blue sky, the tides of the bay bashing on the shore and its mangrove forest. The beach is about 30 kilometers in length, 6 kilometers in breadth and situated at the Lotachapli Union, Kolapara Thana, Patuakhali District. It’s unique as there are no other beaches in Bangladesh where you can witness both sunrise and sunset. Jhaubon (Jhau forest) is an exquisite place in Kuakata which is close to the beach.
    </string>

    <string name="floatingBazar_text">
        The 200-year-old floating market at Bhimruli in Jhalakathi has become a tourist spot.

The market began its journey when traders first started selling only guavas there but in time all kinds of agricultural products have been introduced and are sold here all round the year.

Hundreds of tourists from home and abroad visit the place every day to enjoy the beauty of the market and its surrounding landscape.

Small boats gather on the Bhimruli canal loaded with guavas, hog plums and other agricultural products from dawn. Traders sell those to the many wholesalers who turn up from across the country.

There are about 7,000 guava and many hog plums orchards in the 30 villages in the area, according to the district agriculture office.
    </string>

    <string name="sonarChor_text">
        Sonarchar, on the outskirts of the Bay of Bengal, filled with beautiful natural beauty. Its location on the southern boundary of the Rangabali Upazila of Patuakhali, with the full bay of the Bay of Bengal.

 There is a seven-kilometer-long sea beach along the wide forest, there are red capsules. When the waters of the tide rise in the ocean, you can see the unique beauty of the Sonar Chor. The small-scale waves in the coastline collapsed. Sunrise and sunset can be seen standing on the beach of the golden river, just like a quadrangle.
    </string>

    <string name="mahasthangarh_text">

        One of the most iconic and historic places in Bangladesh is the 1600-year-old city “Mahasthangarh”- situated 13 kilometre north to Bogra town. The word Mahasthangarh stands for excellent sanctity and fort. Near about 1.5km long citadel walls that fortified heart of the ancient city contains several mounds and structural vestiges. Of these a few of notable structures inside the fort are: Jiat Kunda (well which, according to legends, has life giving power), Mankalir Dhap (place consecrated to Mankali), Parasuramer Basgriha (palace of a king named Parasuram), Bairagir Bhita (palace of a female anchorite), and Khodar Pathar Bhita (place of stone bestowed by God).
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">Sign in</string>
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in or register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="welcome">"Welcome !"</string>
    <string name="invalid_username">Not a valid username</string>
    <string name="invalid_password">Password must be >5 characters</string>
    <string name="login_failed">"Login failed"</string>

</resources>
